Contact

05462737734 (Mobile) batuhan.tanir00@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/batuhan-tanir (LinkedIn)

batuhantanir.vercel.app/ (Portfolio) github.com/batuhantanir (Personal)

Top Skills

Next.js

React.js

TypeScript

Certifications

Version Control

React Basics

HTML and CSS in depth

Introduction to Front-End Development

Programming with JavaScript

Batuhan TANIR

Full-stack Developer | Native Mobile Developer | 42istanbul Sultangazi, Istanbul, Türkiye

Summary

1 yıl önce başladığım yazılım serüvenime şu anda Medyanes360'da staj görerek ve 42 İstanbul'da eğitim alarak devam ediyorum. Bu zamana kadar bir çok bilgiyi kendi araştırmalarım ve 42 akran öğrenimi metodu ile en iyi şekilde kavradığımı düşünüyorum.

Experience

Medyanes 360
Internship Trainee
December 2023 - Present (5 months)
Bakirkoy, Istanbul, Turkey

Freelance

Freelance Web Developer
June 2023 - Present (11 months)

İstanbul, Türkiye

Education

42

Learner, Computer Science · (December 2023)

Istanbul University

Web design and coding · (September 2023)

42

piscine student, Computer Science · (October 2023 - November 2023)

Atlas Üniversitesi

Fiziksel Terapi Teknisyeni/Asistanı · (2021 - June 2023)